homestoreandmore.ie 2010-10-30

# Privacy & Security Policy - Home Store + More

This privacy statement is provided by homestore and more for the information of visitors to our website. 

homestore and more are committed to ensuring that the visitor’s privacy is protected. By visiting our website, the visitors consent to the use of their information as set out in this privacy statement. homestore and more may change their privacy statement at any time. If we change our privacy statement we will post the changes on this website. 

Owing to the global nature of the Internet, there is a possibility that your information may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area. By submitting your information to homestore and more you consent to these transfers. 

Please note that this privacy statement is subject to the terms and conditions of use of the homestore and more website. 

Use of your personal information 

homestore and more receive and store any information the visitor enters on our website or give to us in any other way. The visitor can choose not to provide certain information, but then they might not be able to take advantage of some of our features. 

homestore and more use the information that the visitor provides for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing our online services for the visitor, improving our online services, and communicating with you. 

Where the visitor voluntarily provides personal information, the information may be used for analysis, research or customer service purposes only. homestore and more will use your data for the purpose for which it was originally provided and will not be disclosed in any manner which is incompatible with the purpose for which it was obtained. 

homestore and more will only disclose your data to third parties who are our employees and for purposes in relation to the services we provide to you. In certain cases we share your information with carefully selected third parties who provide services to you on our behalf. In these cases homestore and more will ensure such third parties only use your data in accordance with our instructions and that adequate safeguards are in place to protect your data. 

Other web websites 

From time to time the homestore and more website may contain links to other websites. The links are provided for your convenience and any such link does not imply endorsement by us of the website nor does it imply that there is any association between us and the operators of the website. homestore and more are not responsible for the data policies or procedures or the content of these linked websites.

Cookies 

"Cookies" are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser and which may then be stored on your system. 

Cookies allow us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements, to determine how frequently particular pages are visited and to determine the most popular areas of our website. 

You can usually adjust your browser so that your computer does not accept cookies or tells you when a website tries to put a cookie on your computer. 

Please remember, cookies do not contain confidential information such as your home address, telephone number or credit card details. We do not exchange cookies with any third party websites or external data suppliers and only keep cookies for the duration of your visit to our Website. 

Your browser also generates other information, including which language the website is displayed in, and your Internet Protocol address ("IP address"). An IP address is a set of numbers which is assigned to your computer during a browsing session whenever you log on to the Internet via your internet service provider or your network (if you access the Internet from, for example, a computer at work). Your IP address is automatically logged by our servers and used to collect traffic data about visitors to our websites. We do not use your IP address to identify you personally. 

Security 

homestore and more endeavor to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose online. You accept the inherent security risks of providing information and dealing online over the Internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence or willful default.
